unexplained-mysteries.com 2019-06-04

# Unexplained Mysteries - Privacy Policy

Unexplained-Mysteries.com has a firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the unexplained-mysteries.com web site. 

**Data we collect**   
For users who have an account registered on our site, we store your display name, e-mail address, password (in an encrypted format) and IP address, as well as any other optional personal information you choose to share on your profile or on the forums. 

**What the data is used for**   
Your display name, e-mail address and password are required to enable you to log in to and access your account. If you have opted to receive e-mail notifications of new posts, topics or other forum content, your e-mail address will also be used for this purpose. 

**Data retention**   
The abovementioned data will be retained until either your account is deleted or the site ceases to operate. 

**Data sharing**   
We do not share your personal data with any third parties. 

**Data location**   
Unexplained-Mysteries.com (and by extension your account data) is hosted on a managed server in Michigan, United States provided by Liquid Web, L.L.C.

Liquid Web complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. 

**Data removal**   
You have the right to request the removal of your account, along with all personal data, from the site. Alternatively you can request that your account be 'closed', which prevents it from being used but retains your information and content. 

**Requesting information or rectification**   
You have the right to request that we provide you with a copy of your personal data. If you believe that any of this data is incorrect, you also have the right to request it be updated. Such requests can be made using the contact form - **[here](https://www.unexplained-mysteries.com/contact.php)**. 

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a small piece of data that is stored on your computer and that enables a web server to collect information from the browser. We use cookies to remember you when you log in to the site and our advertising sponsors may also collect or use cookie data pertaining to and during the ad serving process. More details about the use of cookies on the site can be found - **[here](https://www.unexplained-mysteries.com/cookies.php)**. 

**Google Analytics**   
To help us learn more about our visitors, we use Google Analytics - a widely-used Google service that provides us with general information such as which pages on the site are receiving the most views, which browser is most popular and which keywords helped bring in the most new visitors from the search engines. This information is anonymous, meaning that it does not record any personally identifiable information about site visitors. If you wish to opt out however you can do so - **[here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)**. 

**Third party advertising**   
Like most websites, we display advertising to help pay for the site's running costs. Some of these third-party advertising companies may use general aggregated information about your visit to this site or to other sites to display targeted advertisements. The data collected may include IP addresses, mobile device information and advertising identifiers. To learn more about this practice or to opt-out, please visit **[http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)** , **[http://optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/)** or **[http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)**. 

**Exponential / Tribal Fusion**   
Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their **[privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/)** or contact their data protection officer via **[privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com)**. 

**Affiliates**   
Unexplained-Mysteries.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com, amazon.co.uk and amazon.ca. 

**Enforcement**   
If you have any concerns about our adherence to this privacy policy, please get in touch - **[here](https://www.unexplained-mysteries.com/contact.php)**
